(Penny:)Oh, I know. Bernadette told me.
(Penny:)Sorry, Sheldon. I know
that game meant a lot to you.
What-- "that game"?
(Sheldon:)Excuse me, Penny, but
Doodle Jump is a game.
(Sheldon:)Angry Birds is a game.
(Sheldon:)World of Warcraft is a
(Sheldon:)massively multi-player
online role-playing...
(Sheldon:)all right,
technically it's a game.
(Raj:)Bad news, the Nigerian prince
may be a fraud.
(Penny:)Okay, well, anyways,
I brought you
(Penny:)a day-old cheesecake
to cheer you up!
(Sheldon:)Stale pastry
is hollow succor
(Sheldon:)to a man who is
bereft of ostrich.
Just say "thank you."
(Sheldon:)I thought I just did.
(Penny:)All right. See you later.
(Priya:)Oh! Hello.
(Penny:)Oh, hi! I was just
dropping off a cheesecake
(Penny:)to Sheldon. He was robbed
of a bunch of imaginary crap
(Penny:)that's useful in
a make-believe place.
(Priya:)I don't know what that means.
(Penny:)Yeah, well,
sadly, I do.